Fuck!
Foul! Are you blind?
Shut up, put on your mask.
Hurry up!
Yellow card next time.
First position, en garde.
Go!
- Penalty!
- I was on the line!
- First position.
- Bullshit!
That's enough.
Go!
Damn!
- He's out of bounds!
- Stop whining.
First position.
I won't tell you again, hear?
Okay.
Go!
Leïla Lakti, you're disqualified!
I know. Don't bother.
You just ruined your season.
There was a foul, wasn't there?
He deserved it.
But it's the ref's call.
Stop, enough!
Okay, I got it!
Nothing to say, Fanny?
You let your emotions
control you.
Like your mother.
- Was it a foul or not?
- That's not the point!
Contain yourself.
Get going, see you later.
Can I drive?
Please.
Thanks.
You asked so kindly.
Ludo's your beau?
Who says "beau" besides you?
No .
- Don't change the subject.
- No subject.
- Are you in love?
- Come on...
What about your date the other night?
How was it?
I'm not in love, far from it.
Yeah?
I answered. Your turn.
You're very nosy.
No, I'm your mother.
Asking questions is normal.
In a situationship?
Yeah, you got it.
Watch out!
Mom!
Sir!
Sir, please!
Please help!
Wait!
Mom!
Hey.
- Evening.
- Julien...
Say bye.
Your Dad's waiting.
You guys good?
Where's the dope?
20 kilos in all.
Wanna play?
Get lost.
- Get in.
- Yes, sir.
It's Fanny.
It's about Sofia.
She had an accident.
Call me back fast. Love ya.
THE ORPHANS
Hi, can I help you?
- Hi, I'm looking for Sofia Lakti.
- We are.
- Are you family?
- Yes.
How is she?
In a coma
since the accident.
The doctors say to wait.
- Can we see her?
- Yeah.
Come.
Who are you?
Leïla,
meet Gabriel and Driss.
All right.
You shouldn't be here.
Leave.
Mom?
Please!
Please, Mom, no.
Please, please, Mom.
Fanny!
Emergency in room 322!
- Don't leave me.
- Miss, please.
So?
She died at the hospital.
Fuck.
- It was an accident.
- No, I was high.
It was an accident!
Look at me.
It was an accident.
- I'm a murderer.
- You were just in shock, Matthias.
It's urgent we avoid a scandal.
And years and years in prison.
I'm not like you.
I'll go to the police.
- I'll come clean.
- No, no.
Listen!
You act totally normal,
but keep a low profile.
And forget that idea.
It's stupid to alert the police.
Do as I say.
Jonas will deal with it.
- So?
- She has paperwork to finish.
Fanny will be at the orphanage later.
She wants to talk.
About what?
The funeral, I think.
Goddamn.
I feel like an ass
for having lost touch.
- All that lost time.
- It's life.
No regrets?
- That's your car?
- Yep.
See you here at 6 pm.
Wanna grab a drink?
Yes.
But alone.
Which of them is the cop?
They came
because they're your mom's friends.
Local police is on the case.
Fanny...
No, they're not, it's been 3 days!
We have no news.
When will we act?
Why are you waiting?
Why the delay?
Go away, you don't give a fuck!
That's so not true.
Got a family?
No.
I had a wife.
- Driss?
- Then...
I'm not interested.
- It's been 20 years...
- 18.
- Yeah, 18.
- Nothing to tell me?
Nope.
Great.
Fuck it.
CHILDREN'S HOME
Fanny?
I'm in the kitchen.
There's no one?
I sent the kids on a two-day field trip.
I couldn't bring myself to tell them.
They loved Sofia so much.
Wait... Sofia worked here?
Yeah.
She moved back here 7 years ago.
I needed a good counselor.
And with her, I got the best.
She was looking to settle down
with her kid, someplace stable.
In the end, Leïla grew up here
like her mother.
You'll see...
She's not the easiest of the lot,
but I adore her.
Okay!
Since the attacks
we keep our service weapons.
I have a question.
- Yeah?
- Where's the father?
No husband at the hospital,
so I'm asking.
I don't know.
Sofia said it wasn't important.
Still.
Sorry, be right back.
How about the car?
Tell me, Fanny...
How old is Leïla?
She's 17.
Thanks.
I spoke to some colleagues.
No leads.
They're still looking for the car.
I'm sorry.
Okay, come on.
We'll bake an apple pie.
We need something sweet.
Damn... the mattresses
used to be way shittier!
Special Ops?
No... "Expendables".
I did 5 years.
Not my thing.
Too many charred civilians.
I do odds and ends.
Some security work for private clients.
Sort of... self-employed.
Sort of legal?
I don't take credit cards.
I pay taxes!
Sort of not too legal.
Yeah.
How about you?
You had SWAT dreams, right?
I made the cut.
Good for you.
Bravo.
Last time
you wanted to bash my face in.
I bashed your face in.
- That was in a dream.
- Yeah?
- Couldn't stand that she left?
- Who made her leave?
She left because she was pregnant
with me.
That's what she told me.
- What now?
- No idea, I got no kids.
Let's talk to her, console her.
Give her a snuggle if you want,
I don't know how.
In a situationship?
Yeah, you got it.
Watch out!
Sir!
Sir, please!
Wait!
Christina Rovelli:
"My son will not take over Sécuris"
Where you going?
Seriously?
I won't hurt you.
Is that all?
Go on.
By the way,
Leïla.
She's 17.
She looks like me.
What if I'm the father?
What if I am?
I'm the one Sofia loved.
Believe what you want.
Anyway now we'll never know.
Honestly!
How old are you?
Come help me, Leïla disappeared.
- You took my weapon?
- What?
My gun! It was there!
Gab, I didn't touch a thing.
Her moped is gone.
Oh fuck.
How is she going to screw up this time?
A kid won't hurt herself.
Age isn't a factor in suicides.
You're a teen psychologist now?
Don't move.
- I didn't mean to...
- Step back.
You piece of shit.
You didn't even call for help.
I was scared.
I didn't know what to do.
I'll go to the cops.
Forgive me.
I think about it all night.
I can't sleep.
Shut up, my mother's dead.
My mother's dead
because of you.
I know, sorry.
Sorry.
Shoot, kill me.
Go on.
Matthias pick that up.
Pick it up!
What are you doing here?
You threaten my son?
Security!
Wait.
Let her go, she did nothing.
You know we can't let her leave.
Don't move.
In any case,
prison or you is the same.
Beat it.
Give me the gun.
Beat it!
Enough.
Give it to me.
- I'm fed up.
- Give it to me. Her!
Stop!
You know none of her friends?
No, I mean I know them all
but not where she is.
It's her!
Where are you?
Just don't move.
We're coming.
Don't move.
Train station.
She was terrified.
You okay?
- Why are you wet?
- Got my gun?
Let her breathe.
Yeah, you're right.
Leïla,
breathe.
This is important.
- Got my gun?
- Leïla! You shoot anyone?
- No, he...
- He shot at you?
No, he...
- Who he?
- The guy who killed Mom.
- What guy?
- Matthias Rovelli.
What happened?
I don't know, I'm not sure.
He got in a fight with his mother.
He put your gun to his forehead.
Fuck.
There was a gunshot.
What?
What gunshot?
My gun...
is still there?
Is it still there?
Are you serious?
Fuck!
Let's get moving.
Come.
Keep calm.
Calm.
If I call the police,
there'll be an autopsy.
Tell no one.
You know what to do.
I don't want to be bothered
for any reason.
Understood, Christina.
No way!
When did you decide
to steal my gun to kill Rovelli?
- Okay, lay off me.
- Sorry?
I screwed up. I get it.
- Stop obsessing.
- It's attempted homicide!
You're pushing it, Leïla.
- You too now?
- She steals my gun and mouths off.
Kids today, what the fuck?
Enough with your gun.
Want a second round?
- Let's go.
- Calm down, enough!
Can we speak as adults?
Leïla found the guy
who killed her mother.
We'll go to the police
and let them settle this.
- We'll avoid that.
- Why?
She'd be taken into custody
for attempted murder.
The kid just lost her mother.
She needs our help.
I have an idea, but you won't like it.
What kind of idea?
We keep quiet for the accident.
They keep quiet for Leïla.
And I get my gun back.
No, wait...
What about Sofia in all this?
The Rovelli kid can't just walk.
Leïla will never stand for it.
Nor will I.
We get my gun and fuck them up.
Sécuris is not a company of bouncers.
They tried recruiting me
after Special Ops.
Biggest security firm in Europe.
And Rovelli?
Brilliant woman.
Formidable executive.
PhD in Military Ops.
Specialist in warfare, lawfare, etc.
Eminence grise
known the world over.
With quite the contact list.
Yeah, I see.
Every reason to avoid a scandal.
Exactly.
Leïla's got guts.
You know,
stealing a cop's gun
to avenge her mom...
Well, the cop is me
and it's totally reckless.
I think she takes after me.
Starting your career as a dad?
You don't care who Leïla's father is?
It matters.
What matters
is solving this clusterfuck.
We'll work out the family later.
See? We are a family.
No... shut up.
- You said family.
- I said shut up.
He said family.
You sure of this plan?
It's your plan.
Exactly.
Police.
That sucked.
Search by serial number
Your ID?
He's the witness.
Good evening.
Evening.
How can we help you?
This man was walking his dog
and heard a gunshot in this house.
A gunshot?
There were no gunshots here, sir.
This is the Rovelli residence.
Madam is seeing no one.
Perfect.
We came to see Matthias Rovelli.
Is he here?
Not that I'm aware of.
You must leave us now.
Three days ago Matthias Rovelli
killed someone.
A hit and run.
Can we talk?
Wait here.
Madame Rovelli.
Matthias isn't in?
What do you want from him?
Just to talk.
A girl came here earlier.
With a gun.
Follow me.
An orphan...
is what we become
when we lose a parent.
But for a mother who loses her son
there is no word.
Jonas.
Sig-Sauer.
SP 2022. Serial number:
S-073-1-2-5,
belonging to Commander Gabriel Stenne,
Internal Affairs.
- Internal Affairs?
- Not now.
Leïla Lakti used your gun
to cause Matthias' death.
First we'll deal with you.
Then we'll pay a visit to Leïla.
With all due respect, Mrs. Rovelli,
no one touches my daughter.
- Excuse me?
- What?
- What was that?
- What was what?
- Now she's your kid?
- Now you want one?
This has to be settled.
- Let's settle it now.
- Let's.
- Round 2?
- You bet.
Enough.
Shit!
Let's take it easy, okay?
Lower your gun.
Lower it.
Kick it away.
This is what you want?
Yeah.
Take it.
And leave.
Stop!
Let them leave.
- We need them dead.
- Recruit a team, not solo.
What do we do?
Fanny, it's me.
Is there still the cabin?
Take Leïla and wait for us there.
Please, do as I say, Fanny.
All of us in a safe place.
Then what?
Then we'll see.
Some serious shit.
That's basically it.
Can we have an explanation now?
Matthias Rovelli is dead.
What?
And his mother,
who happens to be a psycho,
thinks that Leïla killed him.
Look at me.
I saw the wound, there's no doubt.
It was a suicide.
Yeah, but...
Leïla can't stay in Biarritz.
What are they after?
They want me dead?
She has the means.
I'll have a word with her.
- No, Fanny, bad idea.
- Why?
She's dangerous.
We leave early tomorrow.
Listen,
my pals can protect Leïla.
Spare us your pals.
Better than your cop buds.
Quick word outside?
Be right back.
What did you do, Leïla?
What did you do?
What's your problem?
Be happy you got your gun.
Yes, and now that I have it,
it's time to call my colleagues.
You don't get it.
She controls this region.
So I'll call my colleagues.
Can Sécuris track our cell phones?
Fanny!
Your phone, please.
Thanks.
Your phone.
- Dream on.
- Sorry.
He's a lunatic.
Give that back.
Fuck!
Why throw away my phone?
No choice. Safety reasons.
You're such fucking pains!
What?
Look what I found.
It waited 18 years for us.
She told her dad,
so I got discharged from SWAT.
Yeah, keep on laughing, son of a bitch!
Goddamn!
Mine shot at me. With my gun.
You know what? I understand her.
When the cops came,
I was naked and gushing blood,
with a dislocated shoulder:
"It's all good, sir,
a little construction work."
Women aren't our strong point.
I only loved Sofia.
You too?
- Was it you or her who...
- Driss...
- What?
- Fucking traitor.
What?
Don't act like a cop.
What do you do?
Not even he knows.
How did your parents die?
House caught on fire.
I was sleeping at a friend's.
My mom killed herself,
never met my dad.
Cool.
What was the deal with Mom?
- We all grew up together.
- At the Home.
Bonds form.
We were both in love with her.
That created fewer bonds.
You mean, you went out with her?
- Yep.
- Not at the same time.
Close enough.
So one of you is
my biological dad.
I look more like Driss though.
That means nothing.
You sure do look a lot like your mom.
I'm scared.
Now you should reassure me.
It'll all be fine.
Jeez, are you two pathetic!
Really lame.
Not very legal.
Yeah, who cares?
Give the kids a kiss.
Time to go.
You got girlfriends?
No comment.
Ditto.
A guy?
Maybe.
We better switch cars.
Got him.
Go right.
Problem with my car?
I'd prefer low-key.
- Is your face low-key?
- I get stopped less than you.
I get stopped because they're jealous.
Of my car.
Not of your shirt?
What does Mulan want?
Remember the gypsies
who chased us?
No, it was the crime squad.
Same difference.
Guys!
Floor it!
Move!
Drop it!
Don't look!
Get out!
- So?
- All good. We have the girl.
Take the car.
Fuck!
Where are you, Driss?
It's Driss! It's Dad!
Idiot.
I'm fine!
Faster! Shitty car!
Shitty gears!
- Capri coming.
- Aim and fire.
Shoot them!
Faster, he's on me!
- You okay?
- What?
You okay?
Hold on tight.
Where are you doing?
- Ok, fuck.
- What is it?
Head down!
My car!
It's a piece of shit!
Get me closer!
Come!
Shitty gun!
Move!
Bag!
Driss!
Get ready to run.
Thief!
My boat!
Fuck!
My fucking boat!
It's me.
Yes.
Got the girl?
It's complicated.
You mean you let them get away?
Christina, I...
I want that girl, Jonas.
And I want her alive.
So figure it out.
You hear me?
- I must speak to her!
- I'll locate them.
They stole a boat
with a phone aboard.
I need backup, more men.
And keep the cops away.
I'll send you some men.
But Jonas,
don't let me down twice.
I'll send my location.
Perfect.
Find me everyone in the sector
and send them to Jonas.
I've had enough.
I want to go home.
You did well.
Your mother would be proud.
We're proud of you too.
This mess is all my fault.
You wanted to avenge Sofia.
We'd have done the same
at your age.
You didn't tell us.
Got a boyfriend?
Or a girlfriend?
I have a boyfriend.
Who is he?
- How old?
- What's his name?
- What do his parents do?
- He treats you nice?
Have you already...
What now?
What do you think?
Straight to the cops.
No choice.
I agree.
Wait till they see
Internal Affairs arrive!
Got them.
Along the coast.
10 minutes to the precinct.
This way.
Shit.
Fuck!
Fast learner.
We run?
Yeah.
No way.
Move!
Ludo, get out!
Get out!
Hurry!
Block them on both sides.
You're sick!
Fuck!
This way!
Stop!
Fuck!
This way.
Run!
- Driss!
- Upstairs!
Get rid of the bodies.
Stop!
- We pissed him off.
- You go.
No, you.
- We go on 3!
- Ok, 3!
They're on the way.
It'll be fine, it's over.
I'll drive you seniors.
Run Leïla, get out of here!
Now you'll pay.
Stop! I beg of you to stop.
I want to know.
Know what?
What you said to my son!
It's you.
It's you who killed him.
No, you don't understand.
You don't get it!
- He was in pain.
- Shut up.
You don't know my son.
You don't know your son either.
- He tried to protect me.
- Quiet.
He wanted to confess to the cops.
- You forbade him.
- Stop, Leïla!
He pointed a gun at you.
If only you'd listened to him.
You knew.
So what do we do?
I'm sorry about your son.
Step back, Miss!
Ma'am, listen, put down the gun.
Place it on the ground.
It's over.
Thanks.
Need help?
We really loved Sofia
to sit through a 3-hour service.
It was pretty when the kids sang.
Mom must be cracking up
to see you here.
In your penguin suits.
This thing looks fun.
Want to see?
Go on.
Take a cane.
Salutations.
Sup?
Yeah, okay.
En garde.
You gotta attack me.
That sort of stings.
You laugh but it does.
Leïla, give me your cane.
Come here, you.
Salutations.
Dad?
What was that?
Wait, I'll show you.
Salutations?
Are you on my side?
Are you kidding?
- He's unarmed.
- I'll get my gun!
Still.
Forget it.
We can't go on without knowing.
That's impossible.
It'll gnaw away at me.
Sleep.
I did a DNA test.
When?
I mailed it yesterday.
I took hair from her comb.
That's all?
You say nothing?
I did the same thing.
Goodnight.
Night.